Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Statler Hall., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Moakley House. Kane, Robert J., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Board on Traffic Control., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Residential Halls and Dormitories., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  Wade, Harry V.; Tompkins, Daniel J. Willard Straight Hall.
- Purchasing Dept., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  Freeman, Harrop A.
- Sage Chapel., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Cornell University Airport., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  Peach, Robert E. Mohawk Airlines.
- Office of the Treasurer., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  Durland, Lewis H.; Senior, John L.
- Budgets., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Tuition and Fees., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  Ingersoll, Frank B.
- Group Insurance, Hospital and Medical., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Office of the Secretary., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  Meigs, Robert B.; Stamp, Neal R.; Upson, Maxwell M.; Auchter, Eugene C.; Kaufmann, Eugene M. Office of the University Counsel.
- Tuition., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Office of Admissions., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Office of the Registrar., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
- Diplomas., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Commencement., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 53-54)
- Office of the Controller., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Office of the Controller - Insurance., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Deans of Men and Women., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  Brooks, Dorothy V. N.; Baldwin, Frank C. Women's housing.
- Counselor of Foreign Students., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Students., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Fraternities., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  Interfraternity Council; Faculty Committee on Student Activities; Social Problem Committee.
- Fraternities., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  Social problems.
- Fraternities - Deferred Rushing. Collyer, John L.; Kitchen, R. Ross; Gubb, Larry E. Interfraternity Council., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 62-65)
- Orientation., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Student Council., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  Landau, Robert I.
- Cornell Daily Sun., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  "The Press as Seen by the President at Cornell University" by DWM.
- Independent Student Association., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Reports on Students., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- WVBR., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Veterans ' Education., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Cornell University Press., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Official Publications., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- "Cornell Writer.", 1953 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  Gash, Jim; Hathaway, Baxter; Sukenick, Ronald W.
- Office of the University Proctor., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  George, Lowell T.
- Cornell University Library., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  McCarthy, Stephen A.; Rubens, Pauline M.; White, Andrew Dickson; White, Karin. Library Associates.
- Wordsworth Collection., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  Kaufmann, Eugene M.; Healey, George H.; Emanuel, Victor.
- Mann Library., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  Powell, Whiton.
- Archives and Regional History. Fox, Edith M.; Lee, Clarence H.; Harriman, W. Averell; Straight, Willard; Sage, Henry M.; Sage, Cornelia C.; Griffiths, Farnham P., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- Fulbright Grants., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  Kahn, Alfred E.
- Television., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  Kartell, John A.
- WHCU., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  Hanna, Michael R.; Gubb, Larry E.
- Photographic Science Laboratory., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Willard Straight Hall., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Coffin, Foster M.
- Johnny Parson Club., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Coffin, Foster M.; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Noyes, Jansen.
- Personnel Office., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Placement Office., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Solomon, Alan R.; Swanson, Gustav A.; White, Andrew Dickson; Elliott, Ellen Coit Brown; Belden, Alice Bradford Chapman., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Farrand, Daisy; Kartell, John A.; Nabil, Ali-Kuli Khan; Force, Albert W.; White, Karin.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art Advisory Committee., 1954-54 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Big Red Barn., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
  Treman, Allan H.
- University Faculty Meetings., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- University Faculty Meeting Minutes., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
- Men's Judiciary Board., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Committees of the University Faculty., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Committee on University Policy., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Committee on Military Curricula., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- University Lectures., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Williams, Ralph Vaughan; Harrer, Heinrich; Lindley, Ernest K.; Reston, James.
- Committee on Prizes., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Constitution of Men's Advisory Board., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Committee on Student Activities., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Committee on Undergraduate Scholarships., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Committee on the Scheduling of Public Events., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Committee on Calendar., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Committee on Campus Traffic Problems., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Committee on Music., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Committee on Faculty Research Grants., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Committee on Student Cars., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Committee on Necrology., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Committee on Natural Areas., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Pensions and Retirement., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- List of New Faculty., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 33-34)
- Faculty Salaries., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Endowed Professorships., 1948-52 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- John L. Senior Professorship., 1950-57 (Box 14, Folder 37-49)
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  Myers, William I.; Kurd, T. Norman.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  Myers, William I.; Benson, Ezra Taft.
- Dept. of Ornamental Horticulture and Floriculture., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Dept. of Animal Husbandry., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Dept. of Conservation., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Agricultural Extension., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Los Banos Project., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  University of the Philippines.
- College of Architecture., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  Owings, Nathaniel A.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Collyer, John L.; Wise, Charles Frederick. National Architectural Accrediting Board; Quotas; American Institute of Architects.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  O'Leary, Paul M.; Guerlac, Henry; Singer, Marcus; Caplan, Harry. University of Kansas.
- Dept. of Chemistry., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Dept. of Economics., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1953-55 (Box 14, Folder 61-62)
  Sharp, Lauriston; Biggerstaff, Knight; Kahin, George McT.; Sastroamidjojo, Ali. Southeast Asia Program; Committee for a Free Asia; Rockefeller Foundation.
- Japan Society., 1953-54 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Dept. of History., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  Fox, Edward W.; Gates, Paul W.; Perkins, Dexter.
- History of Science., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Dept. of Mathematics., n.d. (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Division of Modern Languages., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Computing Center. Litchfield, Edward H., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Dept. of Music., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  Grout, Donald J.; Williams, Ralph Vaughan; Monsees, Anita; Husa, Karel.
- Chimes., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Dept. of Romance Literature., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  Bishop, Morris G.
- Dept. of Physics., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Dept. of Psychology., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- College of Engineering., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 75-76)
  Hollister, Solomon C.
- Sibley School of Mechanical Engineering., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- School of Electrical Engineering., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Ellis L. Phillips Foundation., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  Hollister, Solomon C.; Upson, Maxwell M. Phillips Hall.
- School of Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering., 1954-55 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  Bard, F. N.
- New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Beyer, Glenn H., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 81-83)
- New York State College of Home Economics., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- New York State Veterinary College., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Medical College, New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center, Joint Administrative Board., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 3-8)
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 9-18)
- Cornell University Medical College -Discrimination., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 19-21)
  Emanuel, Victor; Schurman, Jacob Gould; Wade, Preston A.; Upson, Maxwell M.; Collyer, John L.; Hanlon, Lawrence W.; Hinsey, Joseph C. American Jewish Congress.
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research Newsletters., 1953-54 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Medical College Automotive Crash Injury Research Program., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Medical College -Recommendations for Dean., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  Luckey, E. Hugh; Hinsey, Joseph C.
- Cornell Law School., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  MacDonald, John W.; Stevens, Robert S.; Taylor, Myron C.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; von Storch, Searle H.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1953-54 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; Konvitz, Milton R.; Emanuel, Victor.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Printed Material., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1954 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 31-33)
  Litchfield, Edward H. Name change.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1953-54 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  Litchfield, Edward H.; Emanuel, Victor.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  Meek, Howard B.; Tower, James W. Statler Hall; Statler Foundation; Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc.
- Statler Foundation., 1952-53 (Box 15, Folder 36-38)
- School of Education., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  General Mills, Inc.
- School of Education., 1953-54 (Box 15, Folder 40-41)
- School of Nutrition., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Office of University Development., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Graduate School., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Fellowships., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  Ford Foundation.
- Division of Unclassified Students., 1954-55 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- ROTC., 1953-55 (Box 15, Folder 47-49)
  Dept. of Military Science and Tactics.
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1954-55 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  Kane, Robert J. National Collegiate Athletic Association.
- Robert J. Kane's "Confidential Letters.", 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Ivy League. Peer, Sherman; Bradley, Hunt., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Air ROTC., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Coates, Philip D. Dept. of Air Science.
- Naval ROTC., 1954-55 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Bouker, John G.
- ROTC, Naval ROTC, Air ROTC., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
- Newman Laboratory of Nuclear Studies. Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development., 1954-55 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Emanuel, Victor; Furnas, Clifford C.; Collyer, John L.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory -Newsletters., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory -Minutes., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory -Finances., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Printed Material., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Summer Session. Elliott, Lloyd H.; Weiss, Samuel. Telluride Association., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Social Science Research Center., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  Morse, Chandler. Ford Foundation.
- University Testing and Service Bureau., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Cornell Plantations., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Infirmary and Clinic., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Gannett Clinic., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Todd, Walter L.; Emanuel, Victor.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1954-55 (Box 16, Folder 23-27)
  Olds, Glenn A.; Mendenhall, William W.; Noel, Don O.; Saunders, Byron W.; Scheetz, Francis H.; Thorp, Charles M. James Foundation.
- Cornell United Religious Work -Recommendations., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
- Cornell Alumni Fund., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  Goetz, George A. Class of 1916 Professorship.
- Cornell Alumni Fund. Grasselli, Caesar A.; Farr, Newton C.; Bradley, Hunt., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Alumni Office. Brewer, R. Selden; Lea, Robert B.; Bard, F. N.; Cornell, Ezra B. III., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Alumni Office. Brewer, R. Selden; Wade, Harry V.; Gannett, Frank E.; Ward, J. Carlton., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Cornell Heights Residential Club. Colbert, Robert R.; Ward, J. Carlton; Wade, Harry V. Purdue University., 1952-54 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Alumni Meetings. Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Alumni Matters., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  Alumni Committee on Secondary Schools.
- Alumni Matters., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  Report to the Alumni.
- Invitations to Sage Chapel Preachers., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)
- Scholarships., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 40-44)
- Rhodes Scholarships., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Scholarships., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Sage Chapel Preachers., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 47-51)
- Prizes., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Messenger Lectures., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Messenger Lectures - C. B. van Niel., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Messenger Lectures - Luther Gulick., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Messenger Lectures - Konrad E. Lorenz., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Messenger Lectures - Phil lip H. Kuenen., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Messenger Lectures - Alpheus Thomas Mason., 1953-54 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Victor Emanuel Lectureship., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Extramural Courses., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  Committee on Adult Education.
- Vacation Policy., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Research Laboratory for Diseases of Dogs. Olin, John M.; Day, Lee Garnett., 1952-55 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- State University of New York., 1952-54 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  Carlson, William S.
- State University of New York., 1953-55 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  Carlson, William S.; Frodin, Reuben; Newsom, Carrol 1 V.
- State University of New York., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  Frodin, Reuben; Myers, William I.
- State University of New York -Newsletters., 1953-55 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- William S. Carlson. Syracuse University. Loyalty checks., 1953-55 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- New York State Education Dept. - Degrees., 1953-54 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- New York State Education Dept., 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Newsom, Carroll V.; Nyquist, Ewald B.; O'Leary, Paul M.
- New York State Education Dept. - Reports., 1953-55 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- A Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  National Committee for the Aaronsburg Story; American Cancer Society; American Jewish Congress.
- A Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- American Council on Education., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 9-13)
  Griffith, Coleman R.; Elliott, Lloyd H.
- Applications for Jobs., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Holt, Arthur G.
- Applications for Jobs., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Eastman, Edward R.
- Applications for Jobs., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Keyes, Fenton.
- Association of American Colleges., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Association of American Universities., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Ingalls, Lester W.; Carlson, William S.
- DWM's Requests for Autographed Books., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- B Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Bache, Harold L.; Rossiter, Clinton L.
- C Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Case, Clifford P.; Glennan, T. Keith; Catlin, George.
- C Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  Trilling, Diana. Committee on World Freedom; Columbia University.
- Cresap, McCormick and Paget, Management Consultants., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Contributory Retirement and Free Tuition for Non- Academic Employees., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- D Miscellaneous., 1953-56 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  du Pont de Nemours & Co.
- Deans, Directors, and Department Heads., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- E Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Emerson, Willard I. Eastern Collegiate Athletic Conference.
- Farm and Home Week., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  Harriman, W. Averell.
- F Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  Fader, Daniel N. Fund for the Advancement of Education.
- Foundations., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- G Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  General Electric Company.
- Ford Foundation., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  McDaniel, Joseph M.; Heald, Henry T. Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences.
- Ford Foundation., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  Corson, John J. Grant-in-Aid Program in the Behavioral Sciences.
- New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- H Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  Halley, Daniel M.; Hickok, Julian. Hungary.
- Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  Statler, Alice. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration., 1955 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  Zurcher, Arnold J.; Sloan, Alfred P.; Litchfield, Edward H. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- I Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  Morrill, J. L.; Ives, Irving M.; Oey, Giok Po. International Educational Exchange Service; Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants.
- Institute of International Education., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Ithaca, New York., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- J Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- K Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  Kahin, George McT.; Kaufmann, Eugene M.
- L Miscellaneous., 1954-57 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  LeBoeuf, Randall J.; Linowitz, Sol M.; LI op, Manuel C. T. "History of Cornell University 's Position Concerning Labor Unions."
- H Miscellaneous., 1954-57 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  Metcalf, George R.; Morrison, Philip.
- Me and Mac Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- National Association of State Universities., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- N Miscellaneous., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  National Collegiate Athletic Association; National Committee on the Emeriti; National Science Foundation.
- N Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  Neufeld, Maurice F. Dalhousie University.
- Jansen and Nicholas H. Noyes., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  Noyes Lodge.
- o Miscellaneous., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Office of Defense Mobilization., 1956 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  Flemming, Arthur S.
- P Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  Petraitis, Al; Upson, Maxwell M.; Phillips, Ellis L. "Policy on Private Consulting Among Members of the Staff of Cornell University."
- Questionnaires., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- R Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  Cornell, Ezra; Rockwell, George H.
- R Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  Requardt, Gustav J. Fund for Adult Education.
- Recommendations for Jobs., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  Evans, Roger F.
- S Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  Senior, Maud.
- S Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  Sukarno, President; Kahin, George McT.; Solinger, David M.
- S Miscellaneous., 1955-56 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  Stanton, Frank.
- Scholarship Halls., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  von Cramm Scholarship Hall.
- Scholarship Halls., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Gilchrist, Thomas B. von Cramm Scholarship Hall.
- Scholarship Halls., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Gilchrist, Thomas B.; March, Reginald E. von Cramm Scholarship Hall.
- Shackelton's Point., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Lynah Rink., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Lynah, James".
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Zurcher, Arnold J.; Sloan, Alfred P.
- T Miscellaneous. Taylor, Reese H.; Thomas, Lowell; Thompson, Reba H. Ripon College; Telluride Association; University of Texas; Academic freedom., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Teagle Foundation., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
  Mott, Frank E.; Teagle, Walter C.
- Twenty- Year Club., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- U Miscellaneous., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- V Miscellaneous., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Blanding, Sarah Gibson.
- W Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  White, Claire Andrew.
- J. Carl ton Ward., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- J. Carl ton Ward., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- XYZ Miscellaneous., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Yale University; University of Zurich.
- By- Laws of the University., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
- Board of Trustees - By-Law Revision Committee., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
- Board of Trustees - Random Notes Series and Miscellaneous Material., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 23-26)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Alien, James E.; Whitman, Ezra B.; Griff is, Stanton; Syme, John P.; Peer, Sherman; Gubb, Larry E.; Collyer, John L., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Neal Dow Becker Memorial., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Walker L. Cisler., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- John L. Collyer., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- John L. Collyer., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Fund for the Republic; Case Institute of Technology.
- John L. Collyer., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  Seeger, Pete; Emanuel, Victor; Fast, Howard.
- John L. Collyer., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Wade, Harry V. Fraternities with restrictive clauses or discriminatory charters.
- Arthur H. Dean., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Taylor, Edward K.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Clarke, Gilmore D. Hungary; College of Engineering.
- Arthur H. Dean., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Sheppard, Charles Stewart; Schurman, Jacob Gould; Singer, Marcus; Upson, Maxwell M.; Smith, Lloyd P. Fund for the Republic.
- Mary H. Donlon., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  Smith, Lloyd P.; Bache, Harold L. Skidmore College.
- Victor Emanuel., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  Rabinowitz, Isaac; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Kantrowitz, Arthur; Butler, Karl D.; Healey, George H.; Sokolsky, George F.
- Horace C. Flanigan., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Caroline Werner Gannett., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Leroy R. Grumann., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- W. Averell Harriman., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- John S. Knight., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  Olin, John M. Fund for the Republic.
- Albert K. Mitchell., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Floyd R. Newman. Fawcett, Novice., 1957 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Nicholas H. Noyes., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- John M. Olin., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  Olin Library; American Association of University Professors; Fund for the Republic.
- J. Preston Levis., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Joseph P. Ripley., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Francis H. Scheetz., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  Morrison, Philip; Class of 1916 Professorship.
- Myron C. Taylor., 1955-56 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  Communism.
- Allan H. Treman., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  Dorf, Philip.
- Maxwell M. Upson., 1955-57 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  Mohawk Airlines.
- Board of Trustees - Trustee Membership., 1956 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee., 1956-57 (Box 18, Folder 54)